<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Hugo Whisper Theme</title>
    <link>/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Hugo Whisper Theme</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 10:32:12 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install Hugo</title>
      <link>/docs/install-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/install-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisites Before you begin this tutorial, you must:
Install Hugo (the extended version) Install Git Make sure you have the Hugo Extended version installed. If you are not using the extended version, some themes will not not compile.
Install Hugo Hugo is available for a variety of operating systems and architectures. Visit the latest release page, and scroll down to the Assets section to download the version you need.
In this section, we take the Windows version for example.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a Hugo site</title>
      <link>/docs/create-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/create-site/</guid>
      <description>In the following steps, various command lines should be executed. Please notice that:
If you are a Windows user:
Do not use the Command Prompt. Do not use Windows PowerShell. Run these commands from PowerShell or a Linux terminal such as WSL or Git Bash. PowerShell and Windows PowerShell are different applications.
Create your site Open a terminal, such as Git Bash. Switch to a local directory where you want to create the Hugo site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create a GitHub Page</title>
      <link>/docs/github-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 10:32:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/github-page/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Pages is designed to host your personal, organization, or project pages from a GitHub repository. Just edit and push, your changes are live.
Sign in to your GitHub account.
Head over to GitHub and create a new public repository named username.github.io, where username is your username (or organization name) on GitHub. If the first part of the repository doesn’t exactly match your username, it won&amp;rsquo;t work, so make sure to get it right.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Hugo site to GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>/docs/deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/deploy/</guid>
      <description>As mentioned before, Hugo creates the entire static site in the public directory, so you only need to push the files under public directory to the GitHub repository to get them published on GitHub Pages, here is how:
When you finish the content editing in docs, run hugo to generate the latest Hugo site. hugo Copy files in the public directory to the local username.github.io directory created in the last section - Create a GitHub page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
